





## WHO AM I?

I'm an entrepreneur and tech enthusiast with various passion projects. I'm always excited to enhance my skills and further my knowledge through practical experiences. With years of public speaking experience, my leadership style focuses on fostering open communication and harnessing unique skill sets.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

2023 Student Design Researcher

Innovation, Design, and Enterprenuership Academy at Rutgers

Developed volunteer management system to help nonprofit admins streamline the volunteering process. Met with different organizations across New Jersey to pitch product and gather feedback. Conducted primary and secondary product research, developed marketing materials.

2022 - Present **Business Team Lead** Ampere Spark LLC

Working on incorporating, securing funding, and designing an online presence for Ampere Spark, a startup building a Kitchen Appliance to ease the food preperation process. Currently building and designing a crowdfunding campaign and getting in touch with venture capitalists.

2023 - Present **Marketing Director** 

American Louvered Roof

Working on designing, coding, and deploying webpage, web presence, and social media presence for a roofing company based in Trenton, NJ.

2019 - 2022 **Founder and President** Robbinsville Hackathon Club

Formed software focused community to compete in Hackathons, complete CTFs, and build club projects. Created the club website and spearheaded all tutorials and projects. Led outreach programs and built a workshop CTF for 8th graders who later joined as freshmen. Advocated on behalf of the organization for all administrative

#### **PROJECTS**

2023 headcount

Created a volunteer management system webapp to free up time for managers for more important things. Used python fastapi backend, jinja templating, jsx and react frontend. Notable features include google login integration, google sheets integration, and systematic pdf generation.

fastapi / mongodb / react

2021 - 2022 rvilleforecast

RHS Hackathon Club project. Constructed various Raspberry Pi based weather stations and placed them around town and sent their sensor data to a centralized server which performed calculations and sent the

data to desktop and mobile clients. An API is under construction.

mongodb / Linux / flask

## **EDUCATION**

2022 - Present **B.S. Computer Science**  **Rutgers University** 

Intro to Computer Science, Data Structures, Discrete Structures, Linear Algebra, Calculus I, Calculus II

2018-2022 **High School Diploma** AP Computer Science, Physics, Calculus. Honors Student Robbinsville High School

#### LANGUAGES

English - Native Hindi - Conversationally Fluent **Japanese** - JLPT N5

**HOBBIES** 

I love street photography, weightlifting, reading literature, and exploring local NJ cuisine

# **VOLUNTEERING**

I volunteer for the Robbinsville Hydroponic Farm harvesting and packing lettuce grown in-house, along with volunteering for the Robbinsville Farmers Market. My picture was published in the magazine: "Our Robbinsville".